Kentucky Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty; Records apap401
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislative Activities, 1992-2023
  - Innocence Project
    - "Kentucky Man is Nation's 102nd Death Row Exoneree" Press Release, 2002 August 1
    - Kentucky Innocence Project Causes Draft, 2013 January 25
    - Background of Kentucky Innocence Project, 2013 January 26
    - KCADP Abolition Now! Newsletter "Jury Declares Osborne "Not Guilty"", 2002 September
  - Law Enforcement Booklet
    - Statement of Officer Tulio Torinho Sent to KCADP, 2013 September 18
    - Judge Fitzgerald's Story, 2014 July 17
    - Judge Stephen Ryan's Story, 2014 July 17
    - Tulio Torinho Photograph, 2014 July 23
    - John Stewart "Stew" Schneider's Story, 2014 July 29
    - "The Death Penalty in Kentucky: Time for Abolition is NOW" Article, 2016 January 27
    - Statement of Former Commonwealth Attorney for Jefferson County, 2013 October
  - Legislator Meeting Notes
    - Legislator Meeting Report Form, Phil Moffett, 2015 September 3
    - Legislator Meeting Report Form, Senator Dennis Parrett, 2015 September 11
    - Legislator Meeting Report Form, Linda Belcher, 2015 September 23
    - Legislator Meeting Report Form, Jeff Greer, 2015 November 4
    - New Legislators, Meeting Notes, 2005
    - List of Interviewers, 2012
    - Death Penalty of Individual States, Democratic, 2012
    - House Members List with Notes, ALL, 2013
    - Senate Members List with Notes, ALL, 2013
    - House Members List with Notes, ALL, 2014
    - Kentucky Senate District 1 - Contacts, 2015
    - House Members List with Notes, ALL, 2016
    - Senate Members List with Notes, ALL, 2016
    - House Members List with Notes, ALL, 2017; 2018
    - House Members List with Notes, members who are 'moveable', 2018
    - House Members List with Notes, members who are opposed to abolition, 2018
    - House Members List with Notes, members whose status is unknown, 2018
    - House Members List with Notes, members who support abolition, 2018
    - House Members List with Notes, ALL, 2018
    - Memorandums of Interviews with Legislators, 1987-1988
    - Senate Members List with Notes, ALL, 2013-2015
    - List of Senators, Alternative Layout, 2013-2015
  - Letters to Legislators
    - Conversations with Legislators including Memoes, Notes, Letters, and Reports, 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Filofax of Legislative Contacts' Information, Unknown (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - KCADP Letter to Govenor Beshear to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2010 April 20
    - Kentucky Council of Churches Letter to Govenor Beshear to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2012 September 24
    - Presbyterian Church U.S.A. Letter to Govenor Beshear to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2012 September 26
    - Letter to Govenor Beshear from Christian Church (Disciples of Christ) in Kentucky to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2012 December 11
    - United Methodist Church's Letter to Govenor Beshear to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2012 December 14
    - Draft of Letter to Legislators, 2013 February 14
    - ACLU Letter Prompting to Vote for Abolition Bill HB203, 2016 February 19
  - Mental Ineptitude
    - Ellis Reports on Mental Disability and the Death Penalty, Supporting ABA Article, 1985; 1989 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Exemption based on Mental Disability, Senate Bill 172, House Bill No. 675, 1987; 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Death Penalty and Mental Illness, 2001; 2007 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Racial Bias
    - Kentucky Racial Justice Act Binder, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Racial Bias Studies, 1989; 1993 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Racial Bias- Newspaper Articles, 1995; 1996 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Racial Justice Act, Motion, Nathianiel Wood, 1989; 2003 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Kentucky Racial Justice Act Docs, 1988-1994 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Kentucky Racial Justice Act Failure, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Senate Bill 171-Racial Justice Act, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Press RE: Racial Justice and Death Penalty (CD), 1997-2015 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Kentucky Racial Justice Act Binder, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Racial Bias Studies, 1989; 1993 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Racial Bias- Newspaper Articles, 1995; 1996 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Racial Justice Act, Motion, Nathianiel Wood, 1989; 2003 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Kentucky Racial Justice Act Docs, 1988-1994 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Kentucky Racial Justice Act Failure, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Senate Bill 171-Racial Justice Act, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Press RE: Racial Justice and Death Penalty (CD), 1997-2015 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - "Maximizing New Research on the Death Penalty" Presentation, 2015
    - "Maximizing New Research on the Death Penalty" Report, 2015
    - University of Chicago Law Review "The American Death Penalty and the (In)visibility of Race", 2015
    - "Race and the Jury: Illegal Discrimination in Jury Selection" Report, 2021
  - Studies
    - The Kentucky Racial Justice Act: A Policy Analysis by Janet E. Powell, 2001 December 12
    - News Alert Email RE: "Autry Killer Pleads Guilty- Soules Avoids Death Penalty; 2nd Man Charged in Coeds Slaying Awaits Trial", 2004 March 23
    - "Cancel Kentucky Death Sentences DV", 2017 February 21
    - The Advocate Vol. 22, No. 1 "Cost, Deterrence, Incapacitation, Brutalization, and the Death Penalty: The Scientific Evidence", 2000 January
    - High School Death Penalty Stuy Guide, 2006 September
    - Report "Execution by Lethal Injection – a Quarter Century of State Poisoning", 2007 October
    - Constitution Project "Irreversible Error: Recommended Reforms for Preventing and Correcting Errors in the Administration of Capital Punishment", 2014
    - Final Report for Focus Group Research, 2007 April 2
    - "The Geography of the Death Penaltuy and its Ramifications" Draft, 2011 November 17
    - Kentucky Commission on Human Rights Resolution Opposing the Death Penalty, 2012 November 7
    - "Stories from the Jury Room: How Jurors Use Narrative to Process Evidence", 2013 May 6
    - "Capital Sentencing in Kentucky, 2000-2010" KBA Manuscript, 2013 November 13
    - "Capital Sentencing in Kentucky, 2000-2010" Presentation, 2013 November 16
    - Analysis of Death Cases by County, 2014 February 17
    - Ray Larson - Failed Case Notes, 2014 October 23
    - "Tennessee's Executive Power to Limit the Death Penalty" Table of Contents, 2018 February 8
    - "A Statistical Overview of the Kentucky Death Penalty" Draft, 2021 August 4
    - "Back from the Dead: Tracking the Progress of Kentucky's Furman-Commuted Death Row Population", 2022 January 25
    - "Capital Sentencing in Kentucky, An Analysis of the Factors Influencing Decision Making in the Post-Gregg Period", 1988
    - "Race, Homicide Severity, and the Application of the Death Penalty: A Consideration of the Barnett Scale" Vol.27 No.3, 1989
    - "Dangerousness and the Death Penalty: An Examination of Juvenile Homicides in Kentucky" Study, 2004
    - "Capriciousness or Fairness?" Journal of Ethnicity in Criminal Justice, 2006
    - "Lynching and the Death Penalty in Kentucky, 1886-1934: Substitution or Supplement?" Article, 2009
    - Northern Kentucky Law Review, Death Penalty Issue, Vol. 37 No.2, 2010
    - "Tracking Capital Homicide Cases in Jefferson County, KY 2000-2010", 2013
    - "Capital Sentencing in Kentucky, 2000-2010", 2014
    - "Kentuckian's Attitudes on Capital Punishment, 1986-2016", 2017
    - "Examining the Sentences of Life without Parole in Kentucky Homicide Cases" Article, 2021
    - "Race and the Death Penalty in Kentucky Murder Trials: An Analysis of Post Gregg Outcomes" Study, 2022
    - "Social Class and Capital Punishment: A theoretical and Empirical Analysis" Report, 2014 January
    - The Advocate-Public Defenders Protection and Advocacy "Sandy's Juror Study", 2014 August
    - Kentucky Wrongful Convictions Chart, 2000-2011
- Marketing Efforts, 2002-2020
  This series contains materials used by the Kentucky Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty to market their organization to new members and legislators. This includes digital campaigns, postcards, social media campaigns, photographs, organization and campaign logos, and the ABA modified brochure to be sent to state govenors.
  This series contains five subseries.
  - Advertisements and Promotions, 2002-2019
    - Louisville NAACP Freedom Fund Banquet Advertisement, 2002 October 12
    - Kentucky Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression Banquet Advertisement, 2003 February 5
    - Flyer for Carl Wedekind's "Politics, Religion and Death: Memoir of a Lobbyist" book, 2007 January 7
    - Advertisement to Invite to Kentucky Alliance Members to the NCADP 2010 Annual Conference, 2010 January 14-2010 January 17
    - "Race to Execution" Film Promotion, 2010 March 27
    - Join KCADP by text, Graphic, 2014 April 12
    - ACLU Banquet Flyer, color, 2003
    - ACLU Banquet Flyer, black and white, 2003
    - KCADP Engagement Tool with 2019 Agenda, draft
  - Digital Advertising Campaigns
    - Digital Advertisment, 300x250, Cost, Undated
    - Digital Advertisment, 300x100, Cost, Undated
    - Digital Advertisment, 160x600, Cost, Undated
    - Digital Advertisment, 728x90, Cost, Undated
    - Digital Advertisment, 320x100, Cost, Undated
    - House Members Home Addresses with Districts, Undated
    - Senate Members Home Addresses with Districts, Undated
  - Logos
    - Race to Execution Logo, 2007
    - KCADP "Aboliton Now!" Logo, 2008
    - KCADP Gray Logo, Large, 2009
    - KCADP Gray Logo, Small, 2009
    - KCADP, Multicolor Logo, Large, 2009
    - KCADP No Text Logo, Large, 2009
    - KCADP No Text Logo, Small, 2009
    - KCADP No Text Logo, For Web, 2009
    - KCADP, Multicolor Logo, Small, 2009
    - KCADP, Multicolor Logo, For Web, 2009
    - KCADP No Text Logo, Gray, Large, 2009
    - KCADP No Text Logo, Gray, Small, 2009
    - KCADP Logo Notes, 2009
    - KCADP Logo for Constant Contact, 2012
  - Photographs
    - Chandler, Cropped, 2003 July 3
    - Don Johnson, 2004 February 14
    - Photographs, Misc, 1965-2022
    - Fundraising Pie Chart, with labels, 2003 May 1
    - Fundraising Pie Chart, with key, 2003 May 1
    - Annual Meeting Photos, 2003
    - Baze Booking Photograph, cropped, 2004 August 28
    - Baze Booking Photograph, 2004 August 28
    - Bowling TC Booking Photograph, cropped, 2004 August 28
    - Bowling TC Booking Photograph, 2004 August 28
    - Chandler Photo, 2003 July 3
    - Pat Soloman, black and white, 2003 September 1
    - Paul Patton Official Photograph, 2003 July 2
    - Paul Patton Official Photograph, cropped, 2003 July 2
    - Ruth Stevens Photograph black and white, 2003 September 6
    - Stanford headshot, retouched, 2003 July 1
    - Stanford Wegenast, 2002 September 14
    - Just Creations Logo, 2003 March 9
    - Melendez Louisville, 2003 May 1
    - Melendez Louisville, Cropped, 2003 May 2
    - Murder Victim's Family Rights, 2003 March 7
    - NCADP Logo, 2003 May 1
    - Members at Protest, 2020 July 19
    - Russel Headshot, 2021 April 24
    - Russel Headshot, cropped, 2021 April 24
    - Tialisha Headshot, 2021 April 24
    - Rally Images, 2003
    - Bowling Rally Photos by Andra, 2004 December 12
    - Dennis Archer Press Conference, 1999 December 31
    - Henderson Rally, 2003
    - Steve Bright Speaks at Annual Meeting, 2002 October 12
  - Print Publications
    - "The Death Penalty: Which Way to Go?" Brochure, draft notes, 2002 July 9
    - "The Death Penalty: Which Way to Go?" Brochure, 2002 October 23
    - "It's Time to Re-Think the Death Penalty in Kentucky" Brochure, 2009 August 16
    - Brochure Addition Inside Press Quality, 2012 July 18
    - Brochure Addition Outside Press Quality, 2012 July 19
    - Postcard for Govenor, 2012 August 8
    - Kentucky Assessment Report on the Death Penalty Brochure, with Maryland Update, 2011 December
    - Kentucky Assessment Report on the Death Penalty Brochure, Press Quality, 2011 December
    - Kentucky Assessment Report on the Death Penalty Pamphlet, 2011 December
    - Kentucky Assessment Report on the Death Penalty Pamphlet, 2011 December
  - Social Media
    - Zach Everson, Digital Marketing Invoice Number 368, 2011 August 31
    - Zach Everson, Digital Marketing Invoice Number 386, 2011 September 30
    - Zach Everson, Digital Marketing Invoice Number 388, 2011 October 31
    - Zach Everson, Digital Marketing Invoice Number 436, 2012 July 2
    - Facebook Campaign Results, 2014 April 1-2014 November 11
    - Facebook Boosted Post Results, 2016 January 13
- Partnerships with Related Organizations, 1976-2022
  This series contains seven subseries.
  This series contains the partner organizations that the Kentucky Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty worked with as a part of their advocacy efforts, including: the American Bar Association, the American Law Institute, Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty, the Kentucky Innocence Project, the Knights of Columbus, Murder Victim Families of Kentucky, and Witness to Innocence.
  - National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (NCADP), 2001-2010
    - National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2001-2010 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - American Bar Association (ABA) Report Planning
    - American Bar Association (ABA) Abolition 2025 Strategy Documents, 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Follow-Up Message to Michael Regarding Legal Research and Legal Analysis, 2009 February 19
    - Moratorium Press Release "Legal Experts and Public Officials Calling on Govenor to Declare Moratorium on Executions", 2009 March 9
    - American Law Institute (ALI) "Report of the Council to the Membership of the ALI, On the Matter of the Death Penalty", 2009 April 15
    - Press Emails, 2011 July 26
    - List of Signatories, 2011 July 30
    - Talking Points Regarding ABA Assessment of Death Penalty in Kentucky, 2011 November 14
    - Draft, "Kentucky Death Penalty Assessment Project Messages for Validators-Day of Release", 2011 December 1
    - Poll Findings "Survey Shows Kentucky Voters Support Temporary Halt of Executions", 2011 December 6
    - KCADP Press Release "Admnistration of Justice Troubling in Kentucky; Report Highlights Flaws in System", 2011 December 6
    - ABA Press Release "Two year assessment of death penalty procedures prompts call for suspension of executions in Kentucky, Report concludes 'serious problem areas persist': Poll shows majority of Kentuckians support suspension", 2011 December 7
    - Some Talking Points on the ABA Assessment Team Report, 2011 December 7
    - ABA "Moratorium on the Death Penalty in Kentucky, Findings from a Survey of 405 Likely 2012 General Election Voters in Kentucky" Presentation, 2011 December 13
    - The Record Newsletter Article "Panel says 'suspend death penalty", 2011 December 15
    - The Record Newsletter Editorial "End the death penalty", 2011 December 15
    - Sample Letters/Op-Ed Texts Regarding "ABA, Kentucky Assessment Team, Use of Capital Punishment in Kentucky", 2011 December 22
    - ABA Assessment Former Prosecutors Op-Ed "Kentucky's death penalty process must be reformed…NOW", 2012 March 6
    - Lexington Herald-Leader Op-Ed "Prosecutors: Ky. Capital punishment unfair", 2012 March 7
    - KY Executive Summary of Report, 2019 December 23
    - "Evaluating Fairness and Accuracy in State Death Penalty Systems: The Kentucky Death Penalty Assessment Report, An Analysis of Kentucky's Death Penalty Laws, Procedures, and Practices", 2011 December
    - Kentucky Assessment Report on the Death Penalty, Pamphlet, 2011 December
    - "Former Govenors and Former Prosecutors, Call for Reform of the Administration of the Death Penalty in KY and Call Govenor to Declare Moratorium on Executions until that Reform Occurs", 2011 December
    - Kentucky Death Sentences Imposed, Reversed & Commuted, 1976-2011
    - ABA "Banners From a Survey of 405 Likely 2012 Voters in Kentucky" Report, 2011 November 30-2011 December 4
  - American Law Institute
    - "America Law Institute, Report of the Council to the Membership of the American Law Institute on the Matter of the Death Penalty", 2009 April 15
  - Conservatives Concerned
    - Heleringer Quotes, 2013 July 31
    - List of Potential Resources from M Hyden, 2013 September 14
    - Agenda for Meeting on Conservative Outreach, 2013 September 24
    - "A Conservative's Case for Repeal of the Death Penalty" by State Rep. David Floyd, 2014 February 12
    - "DYCHE- Conservatives Against the Death Penalty" Article, 2014 February 17; 2014 February 18
    - Mike Janocik Radio Show, Interview with Rep. David Floyd and two representatives from Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty, 2014 February 24
    - Letter to the Honorable Mr. Floyd Regarding his Article About the Death Penalty, 2014 March 7
    - Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty, Palm Card Print Quality, 2014 April 21
    - Document of Ideas and Actions Not Yet Implemented, 2014 April 21
    - Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty, Cost Factsheet, black and white, 2014 April 21
    - Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty, Fairness Factsheet, black and white, 2014 April 21
    - Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty, Innocence Factsheet, black and white, 2014 April 21
    - Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty, Public Safety Factsheet, black and white, 2014 April 21
    - Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty, Victims Factsheet, black and white, 2014 April 21
    - Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty, Overview Factsheet, black and white, 2014 April 22
    - New York Daily News Article, "The Conservative Case Against the Death Penalty: Executions are getting harder and harder to defend", 2014 May 6
    - Northern Kentucky Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty, 2015 August 27
    - "Launching Conservative Voices in the Media, NC Case Study: North Carolina Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty" Presentation, 2015 September 28
    - "Launching Conservative Voices in the Media, NC Case Study: North Carolina Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty" Presentation Outline, 2015 October 6
    - Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty, Signup Form, 2015 October 22
    - Job Description of "Kentucky Consertvatives Concerned About the Death Penalty Coordinator" for Tide Grant, 2016 February 4
    - "The Republican Party, Conservatives, and the Future of Capital Punishment" Articvle by Ben Jones, 2017 August 7
    - "Big Republican Names- including potential 2015 candidates-among donors in 32nd House Dist. GOP Primary" Article, 2018 April 25
    - Notes from Meeting with Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty, 2013
    - David Floyd Biography, 2014
  - Kentucky Innocence Project
    - Background of Kentucky Innocence Project, 2011 January 6
    - The Innocence Project Identified List of Common Themes Leading Causes of Wrongful Convictions, 2011 January 7
  - Knights of Columbus
    - "Resolution Supporting the Kentucky Catholic Bishops' Position On the Death Penalty", 2001 August
  - Victim's Family Members
    - Victim Info and Advocacy, 1985-1993; 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Victim's Families, 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Murder Victim s Families for Reconciliation- Journey of Hope Louisville, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - The Record Newsletter, Vol. 131, No. 42, "Death Penalty put 'on trial' by New Video Effort", 2009 October 22
    - Video Project Victim Family Members List, 2011 June 14
    - The Record Newsletter, Vol. 133, No. 30, "Women Cling to Faith Despite Tragedy", 2011 August 4
    - Murder Victims; Families and the Abolition Movement "Building cohesive, informed, and empowered relationships with murder victims' family members in the death penalty abolition movement" Joint Project Final Report, 2013 June 17
    - Murder Victim Booklet, Proof Version, 2013 August 9
    - Murder Victim Booklet, Final Proof, 2013 September 30
    - Invitation to May Training in Jefferson County, 2014 May 14
    - Sample Letter from Murder Victims' Families to Legislators, 2015 March 12
    - Murder Victim Families of Kentucky Letter from Ben Griffith, 2016 February 11
    - Talking Points for Conneticuit Campaign, 2016 February 25
    - Taylor Decisions Quotes from Dissents, 2022 June 29
    - "Not in My Name: An Investigation of Victims' Family Clemency Movements and Court Appointed Closure" Criminology Review by Thomas Mowen and Ryan D. Schroeder, 2011
    - Marquette Law Review, Vol. 96 Issue 1, Article 3"Assessing the Impact of the Ultimate Penal Sanction on Homicide Survivors: A Two State Comparison", 2012
    - Final Art for Murder Victim Booklet, Low Resolution, 2013
    - Final Art for Murder Victim Booklet, Outline, 2013
    - Murder Victims' Families for Human Rights Article "Challenging the "Closure" Argument", 2011-2012
  - Witness to Innocence
    - Letter from Kelly Tabor to Archbishop Thomas Kelly, 2007 April 30
    - "Witness to Innocence: From Death Row to Freedom" Ray Krone Flyer, 2008 February 21
    - Ray Krone Postcard to Legislators, 2011 October 20
    - Shujaa Graham Postcard for Legislators, 2012 February 25
    - Shujaa Graham Photograph, 2012 February 25
    - Shujaa Graham Photograph cropped for web, 2012 February 25
    - Shujaa Graham Photograph for web, 2012 February 25
    - The Morehead News Article "Death Row exoneree Randy Steidl to speak at MSU", 2012 November 16
    - Kentucky.com "Exonerated man speaking at Northern Ky. University", 2012 November 19
    - FloydCountyTimes.Com Article "Exonerated death row inmate to speak in Prestonsburg", 2012 November 24
    - Sabrina Butler Postcard for Legislators, 2013 November 6
    - Witness to Innocence Letter to Members of the Interim Joint Judicidary Committee, 2014 July 29
    - KCADP "Media Alert: Innocent Death Row Inmate Touring Kentucky", 2014 September 19
    - Public News Service Media Usage Report for "Freed Death Row Inmate Brings Story to KY", 2014 September 19
    - Article Shared via Email "Freed Death Row Inmate Brings Story to KY", 2014 September 22
    - Photograph of Gary Drinkard, 2014 September 22
    - Photograph of Gary Drinkard, 2014 September 22
    - Photograph of Gary Drinkard, 2014 September 22
    - Gary Drinkard at St.Edward, 2014 September 27
    - Gary Drinkard at St.Edward, 2014 September 27
    - Gary Drinkard at St.Edward, 2014 September 27
    - Death Row Exoneree: Kirk Bloodsworth Event Flyer, 2015 February 2
    - Death Row Exoneree: Kirk Bloodsworth Event Flyer, 2015 February 3
    - Death Row Exoneree: Kirk Bloodsworth Event Flyer, 2015 February 3
    - Death Row Exoneree: Kirk Bloodsworth Event Flyer, 2015 February 5
    - Media Advisory "Witness to Innocence Tour Makes Several Stops Across KY Mother Wrongly Sentenced to Death for Killing Infant Son To Share Her Story", 2015 April 3
    - Sabrina Butler Poster for Speaking Event as EKU, 2015 April 8
    - Sabrina Butler Photograph, 2015 April 11
    - Sabrina Butler Photograph, 2015 April 11
    - Sabrina Butler at North Kentucky University, 2015 May 12
    - Kirk Bloodsworth Headshot, 2015 October 8
    - Kirk Bloodsworth on MSNBC after Repeal in Maryland, 2015 October 8
    - Kirk Bloodsworh Photograph, 2015 October 8
    - Kirk Bloodsworth Photograph, 2015 October 8
    - Kirk Bloodsworth Photograph from 20th Anniversary of his Exoneration, 2015 October 8
    - Kirk Bloodsworth Photograph, Edwin TSE Innocence Protection Act, 2015 October 8
    - Rotary Club of Louisville Speakers Guide, Kirk Bloodsworth, 2015 October 29
    - Final Report Randy Steidl, 2016 November 29
    - Final Report Ray Krone Tour, 2017 October 1
    - Death Row Exoneree: Gary Drinkard Flyer, 2018 November 26
    - Death Row Exoneree: Gary Drinkard Flyer, 2018 November 26
    - Diocese of Covington Application Form for Verification of Good Standing for Mike VonAllmen, 2019 July 10